<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WatchListfy</string>
    <string name="title_movie">Movies</string>
    <string name="title_tv">TV Series</string>
    <string name="title_anime">Anime</string>
    <string name="title_game">Games</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_id">Main_Notification</string>

    <!--  Policies  -->
    <string name="privacy_policy">
        <![CDATA[
        <!DOCTYPE html>
        <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset="utf-8">
      <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width">
    </head>
    <body>
    <strong>Privacy Policy</strong> <p>
                  MrNtlu built the Watchlistfy app as
                  a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by
                  MrNtlu at no cost and is intended for use as
                  is.
                </p> <p>
                  This page is used to inform visitors regarding my
                  policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal
                  Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
                </p> <p>
                  If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to
                  the collection and use of information in relation to this
                  policy. The Personal Information that I collect is
                  used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with
                  anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
                </p> <p>
                  The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings
                  as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible at
                  Watchlistfy unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
                </p> <p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p> <p>
                  For a better experience, while using our Service, I
                  may require you to provide us with certain personally
                  identifiable information, including but not limited to email, username. The information that
                  I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
                </p> <div><p>
                    The app does use third-party services that may collect
                    information used to identify you.
                  </p> <p>
                    Link to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used
                    by the app
                  </p> <ul><li><a href="https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google Play Services</a></li><!----><li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google Analytics for Firebase</a></li><li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Firebase Crashlytics</a></li><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><li><a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/privacy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">RevenueCat</a></li></ul></div> <p><strong>Log Data</strong></p> <p>
                  I want to inform you that whenever you
                  use my Service, in a case of an error in the app
                  I collect data and information (through third-party
                  products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may
                  include information such as your device Internet Protocol
                  (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the
                  configuration of the app when utilizing my Service,
                  the time and date of your use of the Service, and other
                  statistics.
                </p> <p><strong>Cookies</strong></p> <p>
                  Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are
                  commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent
                  to your browser from the websites that you visit and are
                  stored on your device"s internal memory.
                </p> <p>
                  This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However,
                  the app may use third-party code and libraries that use
                  “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
                  You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies
                  and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you
                  choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some
                  portions of this Service.
                </p> <p><strong>Service Providers</strong></p> <p>
                  I may employ third-party companies and
                  individuals due to the following reasons:
                </p> <ul><li>To facilitate our Service;</li> <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li> <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li> <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li></ul> <p>
                  I want to inform users of this Service
                  that these third parties have access to their Personal
                  Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to
                  them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to
                  disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
                </p> <p><strong>Security</strong></p> <p>
                  I value your trust in providing us your
                  Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially
                  acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method
                  of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic
                  storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot
                  guarantee its absolute security.
                </p> <p><strong>Links to Other Sites</strong></p> <p>
                  This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on
                  a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note
                  that these external sites are not operated by me.
                  Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the
                  Privacy Policy of these websites. I have
                  no control over and assume no responsibility for the content,
                  privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or
                  services.
                </p> <p><strong>Children’s Privacy</strong></p> <div><p>
                    These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13.
                    I do not knowingly collect personally
                    identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. In the case
                    I discover that a child under 13 has provided
                    me with personal information, I immediately
                    delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian
                    and you are aware that your child has provided us with
                    personal information, please contact me so that
                    I will be able to do the necessary actions.
                  </p></div> <!----> <p><strong>Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p> <p>
                  I may update our Privacy Policy from
                  time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                  periodically for any changes. I will
                  notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on
                  this page.
                </p> <p>This policy is effective as of 2023-08-14</p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                  If you have any questions or suggestions about my
                  Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at mrntlu@gmail.com.
                </p>
    </body>
    </html>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">
        <![CDATA[
        <!DOCTYPE html>
    <html>
    <head>
      <meta charset="utf-8">
      <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width">
    </head>
    <body>
    <strong>Terms &amp; Conditions</strong> <p>
                  By downloading or using the app, these terms will
                  automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore
                  that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not
                  allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or
                  our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to
                  extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try
                  to translate the app into other languages or make derivative
                  versions. The app itself, and all the trademarks, copyright,
                  database rights, and other intellectual property rights related
                  to it, still belong to MrNtlu.
                </p> <p>
                  MrNtlu is committed to ensuring that the app is
                  as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we
                  reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for
                  its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never
                  charge you for the app or its services without making it very
                  clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
                </p> <p>
                  The Watchlistfy app stores and processes personal data that
                  you have provided to us, to provide my
                  Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and
                  access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do
                  not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of
                  removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the
                  official operating system of your device. It could make your
                  phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs,
                  compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean
                  that the Watchlistfy app won’t work properly or at all.
                </p> <div><p>
                    The app does use third-party services that declare their
                    Terms and Conditions.
                  </p> <p>
                    Link to Terms and Conditions of third-party service
                    providers used by the app
                  </p> <ul><li><a href="https://policies.google.com/terms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google Play Services</a></li><!----><li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/terms/analytics" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google Analytics for Firebase</a></li><li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/terms/crashlytics" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Firebase Crashlytics</a></li><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><!----><li><a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/terms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">RevenueCat</a></li></ul></div> <p>
                  You should be aware that there are certain things that
                  MrNtlu will not take responsibility for. Certain
                  functions of the app will require the app to have an active
                  internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi or provided
                  by your mobile network provider, but MrNtlu
                  cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full
                  functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t
                  have any of your data allowance left.
                </p> <p></p> <p>
                  If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you
                  should remember that the terms of the agreement with your
                  mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may
                  be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for
                  the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or
                  other third-party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting
                  responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data
                  charges if you use the app outside of your home territory
                  (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If
                  you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re
                  using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have
                  received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
                </p> <p>
                  Along the same lines, MrNtlu cannot always take
                  responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to
                  make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of
                  battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service,
                  MrNtlu cannot accept responsibility.
                </p> <p>
                  With respect to MrNtlu’s responsibility for your
                  use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to
                  bear in mind that although we endeavor to ensure that it is
                  updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties
                  to provide information to us so that we can make it available
                  to you. MrNtlu accepts no liability for any
                  loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of
                  relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
                </p> <p>
                  At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is
                  currently available on Android &amp; iOS – the requirements for the
                  both systems(and for any additional systems we
                  decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change,
                  and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep
                  using the app. MrNtlu does not promise that it
                  will always update the app so that it is relevant to you
                  and/or works with the Android &amp; iOS version that you have
                  installed on your device. However, you promise to always
                  accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may
                  also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of
                  it at any time without giving notice of termination to you.
                  Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the
                  rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end;
                  (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it
                  from your device.
                </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Terms and Conditions</strong></p> <p>
                  I may update our Terms and Conditions
                  from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                  periodically for any changes. I will
                  notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and
                  Conditions on this page.
                </p> <p>
                  These terms and conditions are effective as of 2023-08-14
                </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                  If you have any questions or suggestions about my
                  Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me
                  at mrntlu@gmail.com.
                </p>
    </body>
    </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="see_all_cd">See All</string>
    <string name="see_all_popular_cd">See All Popular</string>
    <string name="genre_image_cd">Genre Image</string>
    <string name="message_icon_cd">Message Icon</string>
    <string name="scroll_to_top_button_cd">Scroll to top</string>
    <string name="back_cd">Back</string>
    <string name="rate_star_cd">Rate Star</string>
    <string name="tv_series_backdrop_cd">TV Series Backdrop</string>
    <string name="movie_backdrop_cd">Movie Backdrop</string>
    <string name="profile_image_cd">Profile Image</string>
    <string name="anime_backdrop_cd">Anime Backdrop</string>
    <string name="game_backdrop_cd">Game Backdrop</string>
    <string name="add_to_user_list_cd">Add to User List</string>
    <string name="add_to_watch_later_cd">Add to Watch Later</string>
    <string name="legend_content_information_cd">Legend Content Information</string>
    <string name="content_image_cd">Content Image</string>
    <string name="change_profile_image_cd">Change Profile Image</string>
    <string name="next_cd">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_cd">Previous</string>
    <string name="content_type_cd">Content Type</string>
    <string name="movie_icon_cd">Movie Icon</string>
    <string name="tv_series_icon_cd">TV Series Icon</string>
    <string name="anime_icon_cd">Anime Icon</string>
    <string name="game_icon_cd">Game Icon</string>
    <string name="profile_banner_cd">Profile Banner</string>
    <string name="share_cd">Share</string>
    <string name="loading_cd">Loading</string>
    <string name="discover_content_type_cd">Discover Content Type</string>
    <string name="remove_bookmark_cd">Remove Bookmark</string>
    <string name="placeholder_cd">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="drag_bottom_sheet_cd">Drag Bottom Sheet</string>
    <string name="settings_tile_icon_cd">Settings Tile Icon</string>
    <string name="application_logo_cd">Application Logo</string>
    <string name="like_cd">Like</string>
    <string name="dislike_cd">Dislike</string>

    <string name="refresh_cd">Refresh</string>
    <string name="no_poster">No Poster</string>
    <string name="genres">Genres</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="application">Application</string>
    <string name="privacy_and_policy"><![CDATA[Privacy & Policy]]></string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark Theme</string>
    <string name="light_theme">Light Theme</string>
    <string name="tmdb">TMDB</string>
    <string name="imdb">IMDB</string>
    <string name="not_available">Not Available</string>
    <string name="change_country">Country</string>
    <string name="change_language">Language</string>
    <string name="production">Production</string>
    <string name="streaming">Streaming</string>
    <string name="actors">Actors</string>
    <string name="buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="rent">Rent</string>
    <string name="plot">Plot</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="select_score">Select Score</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="created">created</string>
    <string name="updated">updated</string>
    <string name="deleted">deleted</string>
    <string name="successfully">Successfully</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="sign_in_up">Sign In/Sign Up</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="network">Network</string>
    <string name="seasons">Seasons</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="discover">Discover</string>
    <string name="discover_title">🕵️ Discover</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="upcoming">📅&#032;Upcoming</string>
    <string name="top_rated">🍿&#032;Top Rated</string>
    <string name="popular">🔥&#032;Popular</string>
    <string name="airing_today">📺&#032;Airing Today</string>
    <string name="in_theaters">🎭&#032;In Theaters</string>
    <string name="episodes">Episodes</string>
    <string name="watched_seasons">Watched Seasons</string>
    <string name="watched_episodes">Watched Episodes</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="more_cd">More</string>
    <string name="hours_played">Hours Played</string>
    <string name="hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_">No!</string>
    <string name="platforms">Platforms</string>
    <string name="release_date">Release Date</string>
    <string name="themes">Themes</string>
    <string name="finished">Finished</string>
    <string name="filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="diary">Diary</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="season">Season</string>
    <string name="source">Source</string>
    <string name="aired">Aired</string>
    <string name="studios">Studios</string>
    <string name="producers">Producers</string>
    <string name="relations">Relations</string>
    <string name="characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="demographics">Demographics</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="publishers">Publishers</string>
    <string name="stores">Stores</string>
    <string name="game_series">Game Series</string>
    <string name="poster">Poster</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="hrs">hrs</string>
    <string name="played">Played</string>
    <string name="watched">Watched</string>
    <string name="eps">eps</string>
    <string name="diary_title">📘&#032;Diary</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="welcome_">Welcome 👋</string>
    <string name="enjoy_">Enjoy</string>
    <string name="account_info">Account Info</string>
    <string name="membership">Membership</string>
    <string name="recommendations">Recommendations</string>
    <string name="suggestions">AI Suggestions</string>
    <string name="send_email">Send Email</string>
    <string name="change_logs">Change Logs</string>
    <string name="trailer">Trailer</string>
    <string name="cast">Cast</string>
    <string name="read_less">Read Less</string>
    <string name="read_more">Read More</string>
    <string name="media">Media</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>

    <string name="my_list">My List</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="back_to_top">Back to Top</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection!</string>
    <string name="connection_lost_no_internet_connection">Connection lost! No internet connection.</string>
    <string name="please_wait_">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="times_finished">Times Finished</string>
    <string name="input_number">Please input a number.</string>
    <string name="no_thanks_">No, thanks :(</string>
    <string name="login_header">Welcome Back!</string>
    <string name="login_sub_header">Please sign in to your account</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account_">Don\'t have an Account?</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="register_header">Create new account</string>
    <string name="register_sub_header">Please fill the form to register</string>
    <string name="password_again">Password Again</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an Account?</string>
    <string name="please_enter_an_email">Please enter an email.</string>
    <string name="invalid_email_address">Invalid email address.</string>
    <string name="password_too_short">Password is too short. Min 6.</string>
    <string name="passwords_dont_match">Passwords don\'t match.</string>
    <string name="please_fill_the_form">Please fill the form.</string>
    <string name="empty_list_consume_later">Discover new content with a single tap!</string>
    <string name="profile_content_title">🥇️&#032;Legend Content</string>
    <string name="profile_later_title">🕒&#032;Watch Later</string>
    <string name="nothing_to_see_here">Nothing to see here&#032;👀</string>
    <string name="ready_to_suggest">Ready to suggest!</string>
    <string name="_suggestions">🤖&#032;Suggestions</string>
    <string name="write_a_review">Write a Review</string>
    <string name="your_review">Your Review</string>
    <string name="_reviews">⭐&#032;Reviews</string>

    <string name="notification_permission_info">Enable notifications to receive personalized recommendations, updates, and news about movies, tv shows, games and anime.</string>
    <string name="legend_content_info">Legend content refers to movies, animes, games and tv series that users have watched multiple times.</string>
    <string name="move_consume_later_info">You\'ll move this content to your list and mark it as finished.</string>
    <string name="read_terms_conditions"><![CDATA[Please read and accept the Terms & Conditions.]]></string>
    <string name="read_privacy_policy"><![CDATA[Please read and accept the Privacy & Policy.]]></string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_delete">Do you want to delete?</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_log_out_">Do you want to log out?</string>
    <string name="remove_from_later">Do you want to remove from watch later?</string>
    <string name="fix_errors">Please fix the errors.</string>
    <string name="watch_later">Watch Later</string>
    <string name="play_later">Play Later</string>
    <string name="user_list">User List</string>
    <string name="next_week">Next Week</string>
    <string name="prev_week">Prev Week</string>
    <string name="bullet_point">•</string>
    <string name="not_rated_yet">Not rated yet</string>
    <string name="delete_user_info">Do you want to delete your account? You can\'t undo this action and all your data will be deleted!</string>
    <string name="unexpected_try_again">Unexpected error, please try again.</string>
    <string name="mark_as_finished">Mark as Finished</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_clear_image_cache">Do you want to delete image caches? This action will free up storage space on your device, potentially improving performance by reducing load times. However, it may temporarily slow down image loading as the cache rebuilds.</string>
    <string name="clear_image_cache">Clear Image Cache</string>
    <string name="caches_are_deleted">Caches are deleted.</string>
    <string name="change_layout">Change Layout</string>
    <string name="change_layout_info">This will change the layout of Movie, TV Series, Anime and Game content. You can see the preview below.</string>
    <string name="boarding_sign_in">We recommend you to sign in for better experience</string>
    <string name="boarding_text_1">Mark it and save it for later watching and playing.</string>
    <string name="boarding_text_1_alt">AI will suggest new content by analyzing your list.</string>
    <string name="boarding_text_2">Manage your list, mark, rate, and track your progress in one place!</string>
    <string name="boarding_text_3">Discover and search for content easily with search and filters.</string>
    <string name="boarding_text_4">Once you\'ve signed in, you can access your User List and Watch Later from Profile.</string>
    <string name="boarding_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="change_tab_design">Change Tab Design</string>
    <string name="change_tab_info"><![CDATA[This will change the tab design of Home & Discover screens.]]></string>
    <string name="rate_review"><![CDATA[Rate & Review]]></string>
    <string name="feedback_suggestions"><![CDATA[Feedback & Suggestions]]></string>
    <string name="follow_us">Follow Us</string>
    <string name="ai_suggestion_info">"AI will analyze the content on your list, taking into account the scores you've given, and suggest you new content accurately!\n                                \n🧑 Basic, every month 3 from each content.\n                \n👑 Premium, every week 3 from each content.\n                \n🤴 Premium Supporter, every week 5 from each content."</string>
    <string name="more_soon_">More soon…</string>
    <string name="ai_suggestions_once_every_week">AI Suggestions once every week</string>
    <string name="not_now">Not Now</string>
    <string name="get_premium">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="upgrade_to_premium">Upgrade to Premium</string>
    <string name="restore_purchases">Restore Purchases</string>
    <string name="nothing_to_restore">There is nothing to restore.</string>
    <string name="make_request">Make a Feature Request</string>
    <string name="copied_to_clipboard">Copied to clipboard.</string>
    <string name="browser_not_available">Browser not available!</string>
    <string name="increment_episode_cd">Increment Episode</string>
    <string name="season_increment_cd">Season Increment</string>
    <string name="premium_second">Unlimited User List instead of 175.</string>
    <string name="premium_third">Unlimited Watch Later instead of 50.</string>
    <string name="premium_first">AI Suggestions, 3 from each content type</string>
    <string name="premium_first_alt">AI Suggestions, 5 from each content type</string>

    <string-array name="score_list">
        <item>@string/select</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>